[Music]
everyone Kaye here and today we're going
to learn how to do these iconic Star
Wars hairstyles I am really excited for
the movie coming out and I thought these
would be great to wear to the premiere
or to cosplay or if you just love Star
Wars make sure to share this with anyone
in your life who also loves Star Wars
maybe you can wear the hairstyles
together let's get started with Leia's
signature hairstyle you're going to
start by making a center part I use my
nose as a guide and then go straight
back from that and then you're going to
go all the way to the nape of your neck
to split all of your hair in half then
create two high pigtails that go just
above and behind your ear about the
height of your eyes you just want to
secure that with a hair elastic and once
you have the first one done go ahead and
do the second one as
well now just check and make sure that
these pigtails are even because we want
the Buns to be as symmetrical as
possible now grab some braiding hair
this is klon hair that you can buy at
Sally's and I'm using two bundles for
this one for each pigtail this is going
to give you the length and volume you
need for Lay as spns I'm using a bobby
pin through the elastic in the middle
and then I'm just attaching that to my
pigtail then I'm just going to twist
this toward my face and then wrap it in
a bun toward my face again and the
conlon hair does all the work here
you're literally just going to have to
twist your hair into a bun and you're
going to get Leia's awesome like giant
cinnamon bun hairstyle after the first
rotation I'm going to take a break and
I'm going to add in a bunch of pins to
hold this in place jumbo bobby pins will
be your friend here cuz they can hold a
lot of hair at once then I'm going to
twist the rest of the hair and continue
wrapping it into a bun one trick I used
was to wrap the first rotation a little
bit Loosely and then wrap the second
rotation a little bit more tight that
way it looks a little bit bigger in the
center and thinner on the outside then
just pin everything in place and your
first bun is complete and now on to the
other bun you're just going to bobby pin
that bundle of conlon right on top of
your pigtail twist it and then wrap it
into a bun just like we did with the
first side now you can do this without
the conlon if you want it just won't be
as voluminous but you'll still have the
same kind of bun look I chose the conlon
because I practice with every single
thing that I own and this was the
fastest easiest and least expensive so I
really think it's the best option and
klon is super lightweight so you can
wear this all day long and you won't get
a headache from it and once you have
everything pinned this hairstyle is
complete it should come together in less
than 10 minutes but it still looks
totally iconic and true to the original
and I love
it for Padme I chose this twisted bun
from episode 2 you're going to start
again by creating a center part but this
this one isn't going to go all the way
around your head just to the top of your
head then go ahead and split it in half
and then brush everything into a low
Sleek
ponytail now for the bun I decided to
use some more synthetic hair but you
could use your own hair for this if you
prefer I'm going to use klon hair again
and I'm just using one bundle this time
I just clipped it up to hold it in place
and what I'm going to do is take my wire
this is floral wire but you can use any
wire you want and measure it to the
length of the hair then go ahead and cut
it and you're going to to wrap the top
of that wire against a section of hair
this is going to help hold it in place
while we wrap the hair around the wire
and to do that all you basically have to
do is wrap it around like you're
wrapping your hair around a curling iron
and you can see that it creates these
twists like you see in padme's hair
style once you get to the end you just
have to secure it with a hair elastic
once you've done that this twist is done
and you can move on and do some more I
did six in total but this braiding hair
is actually about 24 in long so that's a
lot of hair you could actually do four
five sections instead if you're using
the braiding hair if you want to use
your actual hair you can do the exact
same thing with sections and wire you
can see here that I'm using pipe
cleaners I really don't recommend that
my hair got super duper Tangled in these
but you could do this with your normal
hair and any other wire so at this time
either make your twist with your hair or
with your synthetic hair if you decided
to use the synthetic hair go ahead and
put your ponytail into a really really
tight bun that way we can hide it with
the synthetic hair later if you plan to
use your hair then you're tail turns
into the twists so with the synthetic
hair I'm actually going to go ahead and
bobby pin these on to my bun and then
I'm going to start making the shape of
the bun so I'm taking one section and
I'm bending it into just random shapes
honestly I didn't have any Rhyme or
Reason to this the only thing that I was
trying to keep in mind was that I wanted
them to interlock and overlap quite a
bit so I kept bending things around each
other so you can see with my second
twist I'm actually like feeding it
through the first one that just gets
more Dimension going on in this and I
think replicates the original hairstyle
really well I also noticed in the
original hairstyle that it's got kind of
this oval shape so instead of like
making lots of circles you kind of want
to make lots of ovals if you can I tried
this hairstyle both with my hair and
with the klon hair and I found it so
much easier with the klon hair like
easier to make the twist you had more
hair to work with putting it in the bun
I just really recommend this way
especially if you're really really into
your costume another tip that I have is
if you get a SE bent and then you find
that it kind of falls out of place you
can pin these in place so go ahead and
use your bobby pins to hold everything
where you want it and your bun will look
great so just keep bending and pinning
these twists until everything is covered
and you've got this hairstyle complete I
think this looks so cool this is one of
my favorite hairstyles of pad maze even
though it's pretty simple and I loved
recreating
it and finally we have Ray's kind of
three bun hairstyle so we're going to
start by making a small section on top
of your head something like you would
use for like a poof or something like
very small section pull that back and
secure it with an elastic for a little
small ponytail then section your hair
from the top of your ears to the crown
of your head and brush that into its own
ponytail then you're going to secure
that with an elastic and when you do
that on the very last Loop of your
elastic only pull the hair part of the
way through that's how you make her bun
it's actually quite simple if you have
any little extra hairs that are sticking
out grab them and stick them with your
ends we're going to wrap the ends around
the base of the bun I looked at so much
footage of her hairstyle and I am like
99.9% sure this is how she did it you
wrap the hair around until you have no
more hair left to wrap and then you're
going to bobby pin that in place then
you're going to move on and split the
rest of the hair in half and you want
the second ponytail to sit right
underneath the first bun secure that
with an elastic again on that very last
Loop only pull some of the hair through
and then wrap your ends around the
base this hairstyle is absolutely
something you can do if you're your hair
is shorter than mine I have like 7 in of
hair too much for this so this is
perfect if you have shorter hair then go
ahead and loosen up some hair around
your face to replicate those little baby
hairs that she had kind of flying all
around and finally we're going to do the
same thing with one last ponytail you're
going to do this at the very very bottom
of your neck and again just pull through
a little bit of hair to create that bun
and wrap the extra hair around the base
and bobby pin it in place once you're
done with that the hairstyle is done not
going to lie I really love this hair
style and I think if you were to just do
one bun and wear it as like a half up
half down hairstyle it could be like an
everyday thing or like a oh I'm looking
a little bit like Star Wars but I'm not
going all the way there and that's it
for my Star Wars hair tutorial I had
such a fun time putting this together I
hope that you guys love it be sure to
click that subscribe button if you
haven't already and I'll see you in my
next video mwah bye
a